As usual.
いつも通りね
Good, Fukato.
良いね、ふかと
Masks are also good.
マスクも良いよ
I'm so skinny.
痩せてるわやっぱ
Have your breasts gotten bigger?
おっぱい大きくなった?
It hasn't happened.
なってない
Has nothing changed?
何も変わってない?
Yeah.
うん
It might be hot.
暑いかも
What here?
何ここ?
What is this?
これ何だろう?
powder?
パウダー?
Team powder?
チームパウダー?
It says turb pocket.
ターブのポケットって書いてある
It's been a while.
久しぶりですね
How have you been?
元気してました?
You heard it too.
お前も聞いたもんね
You've heard a lot, too.
お前もいろいろ聞いたよね
Things like lucky time things.
ラッキーなタイムモノとかね
I'm at a hotel today.
今日ホテルなんでね
It feels a little fresh.
ちょっと新鮮な感じで
Did you change your makeup?
化粧を変えた?
I haven't used it.
使ってない
With you?
お前と一緒に?
So can you please open it up a little?
じゃあちょっと開いてもらっていい?
feet.
足を
copper?
どう?
good.
いい
oh
お
Has your previous hair healed?
前 の毛が治ってる?
The color...
色が...
Yeah.
うん
It was terrible before.
前やばかったもんね
I'll live again later.
また後で生きてるけど
Is there anything interesting that happened recently?
最近面白かった出来事はありますか?
Was it interesting recently?
最近面白かった?
What's the funniest thing that's happened recently?
最近一番面白かった出来事は?
I ate delicious sushi.
美味しい寿司食べた
Delicious sushi?
美味しい寿司?
I see.
なるほどね
Lately.
最近ね
recently...
最近...
What did you do yesterday?
昨 日 何 事しました?
yesterday.
昨日
yesterday?
昨日?
Really?
本当に?
thank you.
ありがとう